[
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "تأسيس هيأة الأمم المتحدة",
    "correct_answer": "1945/10/24",
    "answer2": "ماي 1972",
    "answer3": "1946/11/02",
    "answer4": "1947/02/15"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "مشروع مارشال",
    "correct_answer": "1947/06/05",
    "answer2": "1991/07/01",
    "answer3": "1946/03/02",
    "answer4": "1947/04/05"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "تأسيس الكومنفورم",
    "correct_answer": "1947/10/06",
    "answer2": "1947/09/22",
    "answer3": "1945/01/02",
    "answer4": "1947/07/21"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "الخط الأحمر بين موسكو و واشنطن",
    "correct_answer": "1963/06/20",
    "answer2": "1959/04/04",
    "answer3": "1966/03/02",
    "answer4": "1962/02/15"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "قمة حركة عدم الانحياز في الجزائر ",
    "correct_answer": "05/09/1973",
    "answer2": "1972/05/14",
    "answer3": "1971/11/02",
    "answer4": "1976/09/09"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "حل الكوميكون",
    "correct_answer": "1991/06/28",
    "answer2": "1991/07/01",
    "answer3": "1989/03/19",
    "answer4": "1991/02/25"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "قنبلة الو.م.أ في هيروشيما",
    "correct_answer": "1945/08/06",
    "answer2": "1945/08/09",
    "answer3": "1946/12/06",
    "answer4": "1945/02/18"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "زوال الاتحاد السوفييتي",
    "correct_answer": "1991/12/25",
    "answer2": "1991/07/01",
    "answer3": "1987/09/22",
    "answer4": "1990/12/15"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "تصفية حلف وارسو",
    "correct_answer": "1991/07/01",
    "answer2": "1990/12/15",
    "answer3": "1977/11/02",
    "answer4": "1989/02/15"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "Dates",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "قنبلة الو.م.أ في ناكازاكي",
    "correct_answer": "1945/08/09",
    "answer2": "1966/02/11",
    "answer3": "1945/01/02",
    "answer4": "1937/11/15"
  },

  {
    "quiz_type": "Personalities",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "When was Flutter first released?",
    "correct_answer": "2017",
    "answer2": "2015",
    "answer3": "2018",
    "answer4": "2016"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "historyDefinitions",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "When was Flutter first released?",
    "correct_answer": "2017",
    "answer2": "2015",
    "answer3": "2018",
    "answer4": "2016"
  },
  {
    "quiz_type": "geographyDefinitions",
    "unit": "1",
    "question": "What is Flutter?",
    "correct_answer": "A UI toolkit for building natively compiled applications",
    "answer2": "A database management system",
    "answer3": "An operating system",
    "answer4": "A type of cloud service"
  }
]
